wpchats.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy of WPChats

At wpchats.com, our visitor’s security and privacy is our first priority. wpchats.com will never collect any of your personal information such as last name, first name, email id, postal address and telephone number. In some instance, if require we collect the data about you. Our privacy policy will help you to know how we collect and store your personal information that is provided to us.

### Information We Collect

 **Personal Information**

We collect your personal information such as name and email address when you contact us through the online form. We ensure that all your personal information will be confidential and it will not share with any other parties.

 **Cookies**

We collect general information from the cookies when you use wpchats.com in your browsers such as the browser you are using, an operating system that you are using, your IP address, your location such as city, state, and country. Cookies will not store any other personal information about you unless you provided while filling the online form.

 _It will not be shared with any third party for any purpose._

 **Use of your Personal Information**

We use your personal information just to send information about wpchats.com. We may send you some of the promotional material of our partner’s offers, deals, tutorials and latest news, or we may use your email id to contact you if necessary. To protect our partners and us from fraud, we may use your IP address.

 **Policy Revision**

We will promptly communicate on this website when there is any change in our privacy policy.

 **General**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy statement, Please contact us on hsuren@me.com
